{
    "subject": "resource/Homonotichthys",
    "predicate": "property/superclassis",
    "object": "resource/Osteichthyes",
    "human_readable": "Homonotichthys is a subclass of Osteichthyes.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9394113421440125,
            "question": "Are all members of Osteichthyes subclasses of Homonotichthys?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8852294683456421,
            "question": "What are some examples of other subclasses within Osteichthyes besides Homonotichthys?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8341675400733948,
            "question": "Give an example of another subclass within Osteichthyes."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7308540940284729,
            "question": "What class does Homonotichthys belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6875515580177307,
            "question": "Can you name a specific type of fish that is NOT a subclass of Osteichthyes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6170974969863892,
            "question": "What are some characteristics of Osteichthyes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.609843373298645,
            "question": "Is Homonotichthys a type of bony fish?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49340516328811646,
            "question": "How does the classification of Homonotichthys help us understand its biology?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42756664752960205,
            "question": "To which larger category of fish does Homonotichthys belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.07190849632024765,
            "question": "What is the scientific name for bony fish?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Homonotichthys is a subclass of Osteichthyes.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4263_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which larger category of fish does Homonotichthys belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4263_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the classification of Homonotichthys help us understand its biology?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4263_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Homonotichthys a type of bony fish?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4263_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4263_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4263_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4263_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4263_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4263_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4263_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4263_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4263_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4263_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4263_40.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provided do not contain any information that suggests \"Homonotichthys\" is a subclass of Osteichthyes. The context focuses on describing the characteristics, classification, and diversity of Osteichthyes (bony fish) but does not mention \"Homonotichthys.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}